nice to meet you.
初めまして
I wish I could tell you, but where are you going back to?
もし言えたらいいんだけど、どこに帰っているとか言える?
What subject are you studying?
何系勉強してるの?
I'm studying nursing.
看護系勉強してます
In the future, I want to go into nursing or medicine or something like that.
将来はそういう看護とか医療とかそういうふうに行きたいと
Gatsu and Sankuro.
ガ ツとかサンクロやったり
Do you have a part-time job or something?
なんかあの...バイトとかをしてるの?
What system are you using?
何系でしてるの?
Do you like anime?
アニメ好きなの?
What kind of series do you like?
何系は好きなの?
Everyday stuff.
日常系とか
He's a happy guy that everyone seems to be having fun with.
みんなが楽しそうな幸せなやつだ
Do you like it?
好きなの?
So can I ask you more specifics?
じゃあもうその具体的なこと聞いてもいい?
I have a camera now.
今カメラもあってんだけど
hey.
ね
I think you applied.
応 募してきてもらったと思うんだけど
Why did you apply?
なんで応募してきてくれたの?
Well, they say they need money for a lot of reasons.
まあいろんなくさ、お金が必要ねって言うんですよ
It's a hobby.
趣味でさ
By the way.
ちなみにね
What do you need it for?
何のために必要?
Do you mean you live alone?
一人暮らしってこと?
Well, I think he's a college student.
まあ大学生だとは思われる
father is
父親は
...
There are things that are not very good or things that are really bad.
なんか あんまり良くないこととかきれいに悪いこととか
Am I not doing anything?
自分は何もされてないの?
ERROR
自分はまだ何もされてないんですけど
Well, that's true.
まあそうだよね
To escape from his father.
父親から逃れるために
to leave home
家は出るため
To.
に
Well, that's why I like daily schedules in anime.
じゃあ アニメの日常計が好きっていうのも いっぱいそういうの
Or should I say I admire you?
に 憧れてというか
difference.
さ
Sorry, I said something unpleasant.
ご めんね、なんか嫌なこと話して
ERROR
でも俺もさ、頑張って助けてあげるから
I don't want anything.
なんか欲しねえね
I'll help you.
助けてあげるから
ERROR
好きじゃない人、 夢中するのはちょっとね、
fear
怖
stomach.
い
結 構助
You can't get kicked out.
け られないんだよね
You may not like it, but
嫌かもしれないけど、
It's your older sister, isn't it?
お 姉ちゃんだよね
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いるの?
If I tried to prevent it, I wouldn't be able to do it.
防いでたらさ、できないでしょ
By myself.
自分では
If only I could prevent it.
防いでたら
See, there isn't one.
ほら無いね
You don't have a family, right?
家族無いもんでしょ
Is it correct?
当たってる?
die
死
Because I want to.
に たいからさ
I don't like it though.
嫌だけど
show me.
見せて
I just felt it when I wrote it.
ちょっと感じて書いてた
Then pick up your pussy again.
じゃあもう一回さ、自分のうまんこ拾う
Put your hand under your foot and pick it up.
手を足の下から回して拾う
Fall to the side.
横に転んで
Something from beheading.
仕首から何か
What are you doing?
何してんの?
Since I don't have any fanz, let's touch my dick too.
ファンツないから、ちんちんも触ってみよう
Touch it quickly.
早 く触って
You'll do your best, right?
頑張るでしょ
I can't do my best.
頑張るできない
Sit down.
座って
James's hand touches it.
ジェームス手が触ってちゃう
Stretch your back.
背筋伸ばして
Place it like this with a nice tuber.
いいテューバーでこうやって置いてね
Good, properly.
いいね、ちゃんと
That's all.
以上
Because I hate it.
嫌いだからさ
Then it's decided.
じゃあ決まって
Raise your feet.
足上げてさ
Put your hand between my legs.
手を俺の足の間に入れて
Get behind me.
後ろについて
Only the upper body fell down.
上半身だけ倒れて
Sticky.
ベタっと
I think it will be done soon.
そろそろできそう
You can take it out.
出していいよね
Leave it like this.
このまま
I'll put it out.
出すよ
Can I have a peace with both hands?
両手でピースでもらおうか
Well, I did my best.
まあまあ、私頑張ったよって